linuxize.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Linuxize

At linuxize.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by linuxize.com and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.

## Log Files

Like many other web sites, linuxize.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/timestamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

  * [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/) is used as our CDN to avoid DDOS attacks and to cache our content. Cloudflare is a service of Cloudflare Inc.

  * We use [Disqus](https://disqus.com/) for comments on our site. Disqus is a service of Disqus Inc. Be aware that your choosed name and comment is displayed on this site. If you are using Gravatar your image might be included as well.

  * We use Google Analytics with [IP Anonymization](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052) to track important data and metrics regarding how people interact with our website.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. On linuxize.com several third-party cookies are used, such as the ones of Google Analytics.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on linuxize.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web bugs) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

linuxize.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites is of course a subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any.

## Changes

We may periodically update this policy.

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [[email protected]](https://linuxize.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
